online-dating-ukraine.com 2016-04-02

# Online dating Ukraine | Privacy statement

**Privacy Policy**

**Effective Date: 29.06.2012**

Services on the Online Dating Ukraine Website ([www.online-dating-ukraine.com](http://www.online-dating-ukraine.com/)) (the “Website”) are provided by Dot Com Productions LLC (“Us” or We”) **We have created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.** This Privacy Policy is designed to answer your questions regarding our privacy policies and principles.  ****

**Age of Users**

We recognize the need to provide additional protections for children under the age of eighteen who visit our Website.  To further protect children, We do not conduct business with children under the age of eighteen.  We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 18 on Our Website.    If you do not agree to (or cannot comply with) any of Our Terms of Use, do not use the Website.

**Acceptance of Terms of Use and Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy incorporates by reference the Terms of Use of the Website and is incorporated into and is subject to the Terms of Use.  Your use of the Website and any personal information you provide through the Website are subject at all times to this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use.  By using the site, you are accepting the privacy policy and the Terms of Use.

**Information Collection and Use**

When you browse the Website We do not require any personal information from you except that we use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer the Website and collect regional demographic information, or to perform other technical maintenance. Our Website also utilizes cookies to keep track of your orders and to personalize your experience on the Website. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to track your order history.

When you submit your profile on our site, participate in a forum, or process an order, you consent to the collection, transfer and storage of the following personally identifiable information to our servers located in the United States, United Kingdom, and Germany:

·         email address, physical contact information, and (depending on the services used) sometimes financial information, such as credit card or bank account numbers;

·         your personal information that you choose to disclose on your profile;

·         transactional information based on your activities on the Website (such as a list of members you contact);

·         billing and other information you provide to receive information and messages from Us;

·         community discussions, chats, correspondence through the Website, and correspondence sent to Us;

·         computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the Website, and advertisement data; and

·         other information, including IP address and standard web log information.

**International Users**

If you have provided information to the Website from a country other than the United States, your information may be transferred to, and processed by Us in the United States or other countries other than your own.  If you provided information from a country that grants specific additional privacy rights, contact Us at the address below to exercise your rights.

**Order Information**

We DO NOT sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party without your permission. We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user should provide contact information (like name and e-mail) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date etc.). This information is collected by a payment processing company, which provides highly secure payment processing for Us. Credit card information is encrypted using the SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) protocol and other standard industry practices. We do NOT keep your credit card information on our servers; once it is securely transmitted to the bank - it is deleted securely.

**Security**

The Website has security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We have a secure ordering process.

When our order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software available in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order and order confirmation forms, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing' (in non-secure mode).

The security and confidentiality of your personally identifiable information is extremely important to Us.  Technical, administrative, and physical security measures are used to protect customer information from unauthorized access and improper use.  From time to time, We review security procedures to consider appropriate new technology and methods.  Please be aware that, despite best efforts, no security measures are perfect or completely impenetrable.

**Newsletter**

If you wish to subscribe to Our newsletter, We ask for contact information such as email address. We will send you Our newsletters on a regular basis to the email address you provide. You can unsubscribe at any time. E-mail address will be kept strictly confidential and not given or sold to anyone except as required by law.

**Third Parties**

We do not sell, rent, share, or otherwise give your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes.  Often, companies receive extra income by providing customer contact information to marketing companies. We do not provide customer contact information to marketing companies.  For example, We will not give your address to junk mail (“direct marketing”) companies or email marketers (including “spammers”).  We may provide certain non-identifiable information to third parties for advertisement and marketing purposes regarding the Website. Such information will be groups of data, such as geographical location, time of day, or other demographic information of users but not any information that identifies you individually.

We do not provide your personally identifiable information to anyone, without your permission, unless compelled by law, in order to collect unpaid debts, to protect your security and safety, enforce the Terms of Use of the Website, or to protect the security and safety of the Website, third party websites, and Our employees.

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information We collect from you. If you disclose your information to others, whether they are our members or forum participants or other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them.

**Affiliated Websites**

We may share information about you with our parent, subsidiary, and other affiliated companies. Your profile on our website may also be posted on other websites affiliated with our company to enhance your networking efforts. The affiliated websites will respect your privacy and not maintain privacy policies or practices that are less protective than our privacy policy.

**Prior Use**

This Privacy Policy applies to any use and sharing of personally identifiable information collected on or after the date that this Privacy Policy is posted.  However, for users that used the Website and/or services before the date that this Privacy Policy was posted, We will apply this Privacy Policy to personally identifiable information associated with the users only if the users accepts the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.  Once the user has accepted the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, this Privacy Policy will also apply to personally identifiable information collected from the users before the date that this Privacy Policy is posted.

**Correspondence**

The Website enables you to exchange messages and share personal information in order to communicate with other members. We cannot guarantee the privacy or security of your information which you voluntarily disclose to other members. To help protect your privacy, we do not allow other users to access your personal contact information. To prevent unsolicited messages, illegal schemes such as soliciting money, and message content violating our policies, we reserve the right to monitor the correspondence that is going through our servers, and prevent certain messages from reaching their recipients as well as edit message content. We also reserve the right to monitor and review your personal profile and suspend or remove profiles which violate our policies.  Profiles submitted in a language other than English may be translated into English by us. If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses.

**General**    
We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time.  If any material changes are made in the way that personally identifiable information is collected, used and/or shared, you will be notified by sending you an email at the last email address that you provided to Us, and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on the Website.  Any material changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon the earlier of thirty (30) calendar days following the dispatch of an email notice to you or thirty (30) calendar days following the posting of notice of the changes on the web sites covered by this Privacy Policy.  Please note that at all times you are responsible for updating your personal information to provide Us with your current email address.  If your last email address provided is not valid, or for any other reason is not capable of delivering to you the above described notice, dispatch of the email containing such notice will nevertheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice.  Changes to this Privacy Policy may affect the use, by Us, of personally identifiable information provided by you before being notified of the changes.  If you do not wish to allow changes in the use of your information, you must notify Us before the effective date of the changes that you wish to deactivate your account with Us.

**Contact**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy and the practices of its usage, please contact:

**

Dot Com Productions LLC

Suite 3978, PO Box 6945

London W1A 6US, United Kingdom

**

**Toll free phone:** ** ** ** ** **   ** **       ** **    ** **1-866-Y-SINGLE** **      ** ** ** ** ** **(** ** ** **1-866-974-6453** ** ** **)**  
**Outside** ** ** **US** ** ** **call:** ** ** ** ** **   ** **       ** **    ****+1 (312) 252-0005** **     ** ** ** ******or  ** ** ** **   ** **       ** **    ****+44 (0) 2030261229 - temporarily out of order**

**Fax: +1 (360) 525-0025**

Please be assured that any personal information that you provide in communications to the above mailing address or telephone numbers will not be used to send you promotional materials, unless you so request.
